Maria Asgari Frederiksen











Profile

As a 10-year-old, I created my first website and had fun with HTML and CSS. Since then, I have always had an interest in coding. I couldn't keep my hands off frontend development, and now I'm using my psychology background as a developer.

With a psychological background and my technical knowledge, I strive to understand the users' needs, thus creating user-friendly solutions. I focus on building good relationships with colleagues, business partners, and customers, and I contribute to fostering a positive atmosphere in the workplace.

Competencies



















IT Certificates



Microsoft Azure fundamentals



Plesk Obsidian Professional

Education

Aarhus University, cand.psych. 2014 - 2019

Free time

Friends, family, and Latin dancing



Languages



Danish – Native



Reference

Available upon request.

Work experience

Frontend Developer Aug. 2023 – Jan. 2024

Tryg • Project

- app development in dart (Flutter)
- experience with scrum

Self-Study Unemployment

online Courses: Vue.js, HTML, CSS & JavaScript

IT support

May 2022 – Dec. 2023

Jan. 2023 - June 2023

team-blue • full-time

- DNS and domain management
- troubleshooting on email solutions and websites
- problem-solving approach to tasks
- customer Service

Psychologist

Aug. 2020 - Sep. 2021

Børnefamilieenheden Næstved • full-time

- process management for consultations
- collaboration with various professional groups

Waiter and bartender

2009 - 2020

Restaurant industry • part-time

- experience with sales and customer service
- used to maintaining an overview